## **GAL PERLMUTTER**

galper70@gmail.com | 0545942828

## **MY PORTFOLIO**

UX UI professional with experience in team leadership and working with demanding clients. I am a doer, and my forte is making things happen through hard work, creative problem solving and ability to understand and motivate people around me. My people skills will also help me to be in the user's shoes, to optimize interface experience, flow and retention.

## Education

2022

Codesigner College | Tel Aviv, Israel

UX UI Design program-

The degree covered the following subjects:

UX (72 hours), UI (60 hours), Figma programming, Photoshop.

My projects involved designing an interface for use across multiple platforms (mobile, desktop, tablet) while maintaining the same design and user language. I was focused on creating a simple and intuitive interface layout to optimize and maximize effectiveness of experience, based on deep analysis and study of target audience and desired interaction flow.

Ben Gurion University | Be'er Sheva, Israel Social Work (BA) 2019

## Experience

GLIDING DEER | Tel-Aviv, Israel UX|UI Game Design Apprenticeship 6/2023 - Today

UX/UI internship at a gaming company. Collaborate with crossfunctional teams from initial brainstorming and conceptualizing of new features to product release. Contribute to the creation of immersive and user-centric interfaces that enhance player engagement. Through wireframing, prototyping, and user testing, gained hands-on experience in translating user needs into compelling design solutions. Work closely with the development team to translate their ideas into solid tangible designs through wireframing and prototyping. Capitalize on user testing to iterate and refine the designs, ensuring they are seamlessly aligned with player preferences.

Yad Rachel Association | Holon, Israel Social Worker Manager and Team Leader 09/2019 - 10/2021

Had complete leadership responsibility for two therapeutic afterschool clubs serving children at high-risk with behavioral difficulties: Planned, set up and managed the clubs for a non-profit organization. My activity included all aspects of running the program, from choosing suitable locations, hiring and training staff, and setting comprehensive therapeutic intervention programs to program budgeting and developing close work relations with the children, their parents, and senior officials of Holon municipality and its welfare department. My team included 12 people from different knowledge domains, and I was in charge of all aspects of their professional performance as well as the administrative side.

Israel Defense Forces (IDF) | Israel Military Casualty Officer: Head of Department (Army Major) 07/2010 - 07/2015

Led a team of dedicated professionals that provided support to injured IDF personnel, as well families of soldiers wounded or killed during their military service.

My duties included leading a team of 5 professionals to guide them in their work with people going through traumatic life experiences; developing intervention support programs to optimize emotional and administrative assistance; writing procedures; integration of new methodologies.

I worked with high ranking officers, mental health experts, service people and their families.